{
    "id": "c96c22fda04b42d5856bd78e0eabb92e",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She writes better ……………………. anybody I know.",
            "description": "Better is a comparative word. It is followed by than.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "compared to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "34a758d21e7b4b6d90b77f09c8ff9977"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have hardly been ………………………… since June.",
            "description": "Non-assertive words like any, anywhere, anywhere are more common after negative expressions like hardly etc.",
            "answers": [
                "anywhere",
                "somewhere"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b16208d66ec14d49bb57ec3ecd9d61bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have …………………………. met the President.",
            "description": "Never is used in statements. ",
            "answers": [
                "never",
                "ever"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8fb5d0fbecf843a190492b8d4fee4fd1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you …………………………….. spoken to them?",
            "description": "Ever is used in questions. ",
            "answers": [
                "ever",
                "never"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3dbab5c5959e4cbc846b280d51dbb625"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is difficult to understand ………………………… he says.",
            "description": "Non-assertive words like anybody and anything are mainly used with words expressing a negative kind of meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "anything",
                "something"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3911fed4a05e417d908dd724095066f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctors went on strike, but …………………………… the nurses.",
            "description": "To make a word, expression or clause negative, we use not.",
            "answers": [
                "not",
                "no",
                "not any"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5b6f47dde244492cbc3fa476d3887cb6"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. nurses went on strike.",
            "description": "No can mean not any.",
            "answers": [
                "No",
                "Not",
                "Not any"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b6b4e43a3aff4bbf9c73c0f5e6c3f5a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… you say, I will always trust him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No matter what",
                "Whatever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "22f4366b0fa1484f972129de1dc902b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wake me when you arrive, ………………………………. late it is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "no matter how",
                "however",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3be7fa8c4b144bd5ad30e71672d22566"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………….. a great singer than I am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "no better",
                "no more"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8051043f95634ee6a32f43937b6e8f74"
        },
        {
            "question": "It takes ……………………………. to get to her house.",
            "description": "In affirmatives we usually use a long time. ",
            "answers": [
                "long",
                "a long time"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2d0a5d99243a412289446ec32c856c4b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You look ………………………….. What is the matter?",
            "description": "Look is a copular verb. It is followed by an adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "angry",
                "angrily",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "61a694b85623481faa9f1fdd29788589"
        }
    ]
}